goatrance.de 2019-09-30

# Privacy Policy · goabase ॐ parties and people

[Contact](https://www.goabase.net/contact.php) · [All News](https://www.goabase.net/news/) · [Impress](https://www.goabase.net/about_impressum.php) · [Rules](https://www.goabase.net/about_netiquette.php) · [Privacy](https://www.goabase.net/about_datenschutz.php)

For Goabase, the protection of personal rights is the basis of every use. The following sections explain the principles of data protection for your visit to our websites.

## Overview

The personal right to informal self-determination is protected by legal provisions - e. g. Teledienstdatenschutzgesetz, Mediendienste-Staatsvertrag and Bundesdatenschutzgesetz - by the legislator. Of course, our website complies with the legal data protection regulations.

## Guiding Principles

You can navigate our website anonymously.

The administrators and owners of goabase. net have to observe confidentiality obligations. The security systems on our servers are state-of-the-art. Of course, you have a right of access to the data stored by us. We agree [[The System Administrators' Code of Ethics]](https://lopsa.org/CodeOfEthics) in content and statement.

## Extended Principles

With the exception of GoogleAds for non-subscribers, no third-party services are unsolicitedly included, as they perform an uncontrollable logging for the user. These services include youtube and sound cloud links, social media frames, analysis tools such as Google analytics, code for JQuery, fonts, maps, etc. Media content such as videos may be made available by clicking on them. Technical content such as fonts or JQuery libraries are hosted on our servers.

Furthermore, only independent and open source systems are integrated to a large extent, e. g. [[OpenStreetMap]](http://www.openstreetmap.org/) instead of Google Maps.

## Protected Areas

Some of our pages are inaccessible to the general public. This is mainly about further information about parties. As a registered user you have access to this information.

## Newsletter-Service

You will never receive the newsletters from us unless we ask you to do so. In each mail there is a link to change or cancel the offer. If you have any questions or problems, please [Contact](https://www.goabase.net/contact.php).

## Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

Goabase will never make your personal data, including your e-mail address (unless required by law), available to third parties for use.

## Statistical Evaluation

No statistical evaluation is currently being carried out for page views. If this is introduced, it will be Piwik and can be switched off individually. In this case, the IP address, number of visitors, page views, browser type, transmission volume (traffic), access date and time are saved. This information is then not related to any person.

The ad clicks are stored including time, area, encrypted session ID and an anonymous, three-digit IP address. There is no personal reference.

## Collection, processing and use of personal data

In principle, we only collect personal data on the Internet in places that are clearly indicated, such as when registering as a user, i. e. only if you voluntarily decide to enter it (only exception: see the following section on the keyword "Use of cookies").

These data are stored and used exclusively for the purpose for which you provide us with the data. They are not used to target the advertisements we offer (see [Advertising on Goabase](https://www.goabase.net/ads_new.php)).

## Use of own cookies

Cookies are small pieces of text information that we use to control our online presence. In particular, access protection in areas that are not generally accessible is provided by cookies. Our cookies do not contain any personal information, so your privacy is protected. Likewise, certain contents are automatically opened as soon as the corresponding cookie is available.

Of course, you can also use the website's basic information without using cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, although this function can usually be disabled.

## Third-Party Cookies (new since 02.10.2015)

The Goabase uses other providers:

  * Automatic GoogleAds advertising to non-registered visitors[Google Privacy Policy]
  * Youtube and other video providers for manually recallable videos
  * Soundcloud and other music providers for manually accessible music
  * Facebook for the manually recallable "I like"

Third-party cookies may be set by these providers (see "Extended principles" above).

Third-party cookies can be disabled in all modern browsers in the settings.

Last update: 03. Jan 2016 / Translated with www.DeepL.com/Translator
